Preliminary Guide to the Faye Moskowitz papers, 1962-2007 MS2234
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Faye Moskowitz papers
1962-2007
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
MS2234
13.5 Linear Feet
This collection includes resources related to the literary life of author and educator Faye Moskowitz.The records cover the years 1962-2007 with the bulk being from 1983-2003.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Faye Moskowitz, 2007(Accession 2007.063)
Historical or Biographical Note
Professor Moskowitz teaches Creative Writing and Jewish American Literature. She was Chair of the English Department for 8 years and prior to that, Director of Creative Writing at the George Washington University where she received the GW Award in Special Recognition for Contributions to University Life. She served as President of the Jenny McKean Moore for Writers from 1975-1999. She was for many years Fiction Editor of Lilith magazine. Her writing draws heavily on her life experiences growing up during the Depression and her Jewishness in a largely Christian society. Her publications include: "Her Face in the Mirror: Jewish Women on Mothers and Daughters; the "Bridge is Love;" "Whoever Finds This: I Love ,"an "A Leak in the Heat". Her most recent book is Peace in the House. She is represented in dozens of anthologies, and in addition, her poems, essays and short stories have been published in such places as The New York Times, The Washington Post, The Chronicle of Higher Education, Moment Magazine, and the Jerusalem Post.
Collection Scope and Content
The collection contains correspondence, drafts, journal articles, artwork and scrapbooks relating to the literary career of Faye Moskowitz. The materials range in date from 1962 to 2007 with the majority dated in the 1980s, 1990s, and early 2000s. The correspondence series contains both personal letters from friends and fans as well as professional letters to publishers, Jewish groups, and other organizations. The manuscript series contains handwritten and typed copies of essays and stories written by Moskowitz. In the literary files series there are items relating to publicity and appearances made by Moskowitz. The fourth series contains artwork, including bookcovers, and also photographs and artifacts such as name tags from events Moskowitz attended. The final series contains publications such as newspapers, magazines, and journals featuring essays and story excerpts written by Moskowitz.
Collection Organization
Organized into five series: Correspondence; Manuscripts; Literary files; Art work, photographs, and artifacts; and Publications
Correspondence; Scrapbooks; Jewish literature; Jewish way of life; Photographs; Washington (D.C.); Poetry; Publications; George Washington University. Dept. of English; Moskowitz, Faye
- Correspondence, 1962-2007; MS2234 Series 1; 3.25 Linear feet
  Scope and Contents note
  The materials of this series include fan letters as well as personal correspondence between Faye Moskowitz and friends, family, authors, etc. Additionally there are letters to and from publishers, Jewish groups, and other professional organizations. These materials range in date from 1962 to 2007 with the majority dated during 1983 to 2004.
  - Correspondence, 1962-1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Undated Correspondence [1/3] (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Undated Correspondence [2/3] (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Undated Correspondence [3/3] (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Misc. Professional Correspondence [1/2], 1981-1995 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Misc. Professional Correspondence [2/2], 1981-1996 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence with Jewish Organizations, 1981-1998 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with Educational Organizations, 1974-1992 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence with NPR, 1983-1992 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence with Universities, 1975-1994 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence with New York Times, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence with Publishers, 1985-1994 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence with Publisher Simon & Schuster, 1981-1985 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence with Publisher Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, Inc., 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence with Publisher Russell & Volkening, Inc., 1985-1992 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence with Attorneys/Law Offices, 1979-1985 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Schneider, Ada, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Pastan, Rachel, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Kumin, Maxine, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Dame, Enid, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Gornik, Vivian, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Hacker, Marilyn, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Harris, Judith (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Nordhaus, Jean, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Olsen, Tillie, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Rodberg, Maxine, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Behar, Ruth, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Alenier, Karen, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Zeiger, Lila, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Tax, Meredith, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Steinbergh, Judith J., 1993 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Shinner, Peggy, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Whitman, Ruth, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - LaTessa, Shirley, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Klepfisz, Irena, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Lifshin, Lyn, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Linett, Deena, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Segal, Lore, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Schwartz, Lynne Sharon, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Roiphe, Ann, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Misc. Correspondence from Accordian Folder [1/3] (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Misc. Correspondence from Accordian Folder [2/3] (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Misc. Correspondence from Accordian Folder [3/3] (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Misc. Correspondence from Red Folder [1/3] (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Misc. Correspondence from Red Folder [2/3] (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Misc. Correspondence from Red Folder [3/3] (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence with GW University, 1991-1993 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence with David R. Godine Publisher [1/2], 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence with David R. Godine Publisher [2/2], 1985-1990 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with Beacon Press Publisher, 1990-1994 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Speaking Gigs Fall 1996 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence with Artists/Writers, etc., 1975-2000 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Manuscripts, 1975-1999; MS2234 Series 2; 3 Linear feet
  The materials of this series consist of handwritten and typed manuscripts. They range in date from 1975 to 1999. The manuscripts represent stories and events recalled by Faye Moskowitz during her childhood in Michigan and later her family life after she married. A large majority of the works deal with issues the author experienced while growing up Jewish in a predominantly non-Jewish neighborhood, and she often discusses how her Jewish roots have influenced her.
  - A, and Aleph, and a Knobby Plane Tree, 05/10/1975 (Box 7A, Folder 1)
  - A Leak in the Heart (Box 7A, Folder 2)
  - A Stitch in Time (Box 7A, Folder 3)
  - And Go Seek (Box 7A, Folder 4)
  - And the Bridge is Love, 05/10/1991-08/08/1991 (Box 7A, Folder 5)
    General note
    Note: copy of manuscript located in box 29, folder #1-2.
  - "And the Fire and the Rose Are One", 05/10/1991-08/08/1991 (Box 7A, Folder 6)
  - Babel, 05/10/1991-08/08/1991 (Box 7A, Folder 7)
  - "Because I Could Not Stop for Death", 05/10/1991-08/08/1991 (Box 7A, Folder 8)
  - Blood Accusations (Box 7A, Folder 9)
  - Carnival (Box 7A, Folder 10)
  - Carole Ann (Box 7A, Folder 11)
  - City Slickers vs. Indomitable Groundhog (Box 7A, Folder 12)
  - Cleaver and Baldwin (Box 7A, Folder 13)
  - "Completo" (Box 7A, Folder 14)
  - Draft-A story of bridal shower (Box 7A, Folder 15)
  - Edmund Burke Commencement Address (Box 7A, Folder 16)
  - English 113A (Box 7A, Folder 17)
  - Esther (Box 7A, Folder 18)
  - Every Airborne Particle (Box 7A, Folder 19)
  - Every Little Moment Has a Meaning All Its Own (Box 7A, Folder 20)
  - Fanny's Comfort Station (Box 7A, Folder 21)
  - Fatal Apple (Box 7A, Folder 22)
  - For Mother's Day (Box 7A, Folder 23)
  - Forget-Me-Not (Box 7A, Folder 24)
  - From All the Jails the Boys and Girls (Box 7A, Folder 25)
  - Her Face in the Mirror [1/4], 1994 (Box 7A, Folder 26)
  - Her Face in the Mirror [2/4], 1994 (Box 7A, Folder 27)
  - Her Face in the Mirror [3/4], 1994 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Her Face in the Mirror [4/4], 1994 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Hindsight: The Essay of Interpretation (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - In Going is a Drama (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Irene (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Isn't Much of a Farmhouse (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Jenny (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Lean Out of the Window, Golden Hair (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Letter from Washington (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Linking 'A' to 'Aleph', 04/14/1975 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Lost Weekend (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Miss Bartlett's Quotations (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - "One of Us Remembers" (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Originals-And the Bridge is Love (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Peace in the House [1/3] (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Peace in the House [2/3] (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Peace in the House [3/3] (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Poetry (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Portnoy's Sister, 10/06/1994 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Preface (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Presents (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Resolution (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - "Shall I Compare Thee..." (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Spring Break, 07/08/1989 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Squirrel Nutkin (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Thanksgiving, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - The Change (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - The Good Neighbor Policy (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - The Matriarchs (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - The Miracle on 19th Street (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - The Other Side of Christmas (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - The Runaround (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Thelma (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - They All Ran After the Farmer's Wife (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Things Overlooked Before (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - This Time We'll Look At the Falls (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - UJA Reading (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Untitled Manuscripts [1/2] (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Untitled Manuscripts [2/2] (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Woman's Home (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Yard Sale, 08/20/1990 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - And the Bridge is Love [1/2] (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Note: for additional information relating to manuscript see box 7a, folder #5.
  - And the Bridge is Love [2/2] (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Publications, 1972-2007; MS2234 Series 5; 2.0 Linear feet
  The materials in this series consist of newspaper, magazine, and journals containing essays and stories written by Faye Moskowitz. They range in date from 1972 to 2007, though the majority are dated from the 1980s and 1990s.
  - academic Forum, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Baltimore Jewish Times, 09/20/1985-07/11/1995 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Beacon Press, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Belles Lettres [1/6], 05/1985-09/1987 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Belles Lettres [2/6], 04/1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Belles Lettres [3/6], 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Belles Lettres [4/6], 1991-1993 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Belles Lettres [5/6], 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Belles Lettres [6/6], 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Book Passage News and Review, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Book reviews, 1985-1995 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Book reviews-U.S.A. Today, 09/12/1982-12/10/1982 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - By George!, 06/1999 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Buckeye Sports Bulletin, 10/03/1987 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - David R. Godine Publisher, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Detroit Monthly, 04/1987 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - disClosure (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Discovery YMCA, 09/1983 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Feminist Studies, 06/1978 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - GW Forum, 1974-1989 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Hayotzer, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Her Face in the Mirror, 10/1994 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Independent School, 05/1982 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Jewish Book Fair, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - JTA (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Kepler's Books, 12/1991 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - le culte du moi, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Learning 86, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Lilith, 1991-2006 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Miami Book Fair International, 11/1993 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Modern Maturity, 08/1991 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Moment, 02/1995 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Moskowitz, Faye-Articles, 1980-1994 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Na'amat Woman, 05/1987-2003 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1985-1998 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Out of Chaos, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Perspectives, 04/1939-04/1940 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - phoebe, 1974-11/1977 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Pioneer Woman, 04/1984-05/1985 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Poets and Writers Magazine, 05/1989-09/1995 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Response: A Contemporary Jewish Review, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Rock Creek Artspaper, 1972-01/1974 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - The Chronicle of Higher Education, 04/18/1974-05/12/1975 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - The George Washington University Magazine, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - The GW Hatchet, 04/02/1998 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - The Jewish Monthly, 06/1991 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - The Jewish Press, 04/30/1993 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - The Marble of Imagination, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - The National Observer, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - The Writer's Center Carousel, 09/1991 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Tin Mines and Concubines, 04/27/2005 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Washington Center for Psychoanalysis, Inc. Newsletter, 01/2007 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Washington review, 10/1990 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Washington Jewish Week, 12/17/1987-11/07/1991 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Woman's Day [1/2], 01/08/1985-11/03/1992 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Woman's Day [2/2], 04/06/1993-11/17/1998 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Women and Aging, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Art work, photographs and artifacts, MS2234 Series 4; 0.5 Linear feet
  The materials of this series include artwork, photographs, and artifacts relating to the literary career of Faye Moskowitz. The undated materials include bookcovers as well as photographs and name tags from various events the author attended.
  - Artwork (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Book cover (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Book reading promotion (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Habitat for Humanity pamphlet (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Name badges (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Photographs (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Literary Files, 1975-1991; MS2234 Series 3; 4.75 Linear feet
    The materials of this series are diverse and consist of newspaper clippings, flyers, announcements, notebooks, invitations, etc. These range in date from 1975 to the early 1990s. Many of these relate to events, book readings, publicity, and public appearances made by Faye Moskowitz. The series also contains notebooks detailing dreams experienced by the author as well as essays and stories written by students who had Moskowitz as a professor as George Washington University.
    - A to Aleph, Chronicle of Higher Education, 04/14/1975 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - A Leak in the Heart [1/2], 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - A Leak in the Heart [2/2], 1985-1988 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Addresses (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - And the Bridge is Love-correspondence, publicity, catalogies, etc, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Amy Schellenberg notebook (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Awards and fellowships, 06/1987-11/07/1994 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Beacon-Her Face, 05/15/1995 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Book readings and appearances, 1985-1999 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Book readings and reviews, 12/02/1990-09/1991 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Bruce J. O'Malley-The Journal (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - D.C. Commission on the Arts and Humanities, 03/17/1994-11/07/1994 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Drafts of Early Essays notebook (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Dreams notebook [1/2], 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Dreams notebook [2/2] (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Edmund Burke School-students (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Engagements, publicity, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Events [1/2], 1985-1995 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Events [2/2], 1999 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Faculty notes notebook (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Falk, Marcia, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Fanny Hurst review (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Glickfield, Carole L., 1993 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Gymboree article, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Habitat for Humanity, 1987-1994 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Habitat for Humanity notebook (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Habitat notebook (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Haines, Joy DeStefano, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Her Face in the Mirror, 1980-1994 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Hospital abortion notebook (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Invitation lists (parties) (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - I.S. GRC, 12/07/1988 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Jenny McKean Moore Visiting Lectureship, 1981-1984 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Journal-Major American Writers, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Koestenbaum, Phyll, 1985-1987 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - LaZebnik, Jack, 1997-2005 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Literary events, 1986-1998 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Louis Schaefer's class, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Louis Schaefer's Writing Class, GWU, 1964-1970 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Manhattanville, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - McDonough, Yona Zeldis, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - My student writing in Louis Schaefer's class, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Newman, Leslea, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Notebook [1/2] (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Notebook [2/2] (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Notes (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Notes for stories/poems notebook (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Ostriker, Alicia (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Pastan, Linda (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Pogrebin, Letty Cottin, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Publicity, 1985-1993 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Purse Jotter notebook (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Received manuscripts, 1994-2001 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Remembering Jackson (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Report cards, 1965-1968 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Resume (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Reviews and letters of commendation, 1991-1995 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Scrapbook, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      Note: scrapbook is located in box 22, folder #1-3.
    - Scrapbook, 1988-1991 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      Note: scrapbook is located in box 23, folder #1-2.
    - Scrapbook, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      Note: scrapbook is located in box 24, folder #1-2.
    - Scrapbook, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      Note: scrapbook is located in box 25, folder #1-2.
    - Scrapbook, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 20)
      Note: scrapbook is located in box 26, folder #1-4.
    - Scrapbook, 1995-1998 (Box 15, Folder 21)
      Note: scrapbook is located in box 27, folder #1.
    - Scrapbook, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 22)
      Note: scrapbook is located in box 28, folder #1-2.
    - Seitzman, Michael-former student, GWU, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Shomer, Enid, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Shore, Jane (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Sidney, Joan Seliger, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Sklarew, Myra, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Speeches, 1978-1997 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Steno notebook [1/2] (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Steno notebook [2/2] (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - The Leeway Foundation, 1995-1998 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Thesis notebook (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Vinst, Judith (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Whoever Finds This: I Love You (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Scrapbook, 1985 [1/3] (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook, 1985 [2/3] (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook, 1985 [3/3] (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook, 1988-1991 [1/2] (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook, 1988-1991 [2/2] (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook, 1990-1991 [1/2] (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook, 1990-1991 [2/2] (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook, 1994-1995 [1/2] (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook, 1994-1995 [2/2] (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook, 1995-1996 [1/4] (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook, 1995-1996 [2/4] (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook, 1995-1996 [3/4] (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook, 1995-1996 [4/4] (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook, 1995-1998 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook, 2002-2003 [1/2] (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook, 2002-2003 [2/2] (Box 28, Folder 2)